{
    "id": "bf7d5d40795d43009eafc19fbc4c7ef1",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She awaited the arrival of her ………………………….. from Europe.",
            "description": "Kinsmen means blood relative.",
            "answers": [
                "kinsmen",
                "kindred"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5f1b345a42934a71ada0fee88e323757"
        },
        {
            "question": "We were ………………………………….. spirits and were quite compatible.",
            "description": "Kindred means similar or matching.",
            "answers": [
                "kindred",
                "kinsmen"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f1f81a2b909947ffb21aa0ef451b6559"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I had her knack …………………………. cooking.",
            "description": "Knack takes the preposition for.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "56c1d109cee748e38762e6271016e4b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was quite ……………………………. about current events.",
            "description": "Knowledgeable means well-informed or conversant with.",
            "answers": [
                "known",
                "knowledgeable",
                "knowledge"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f69d2669d5344496af4c84c99dba91af"
        },
        {
            "question": "Kudos ………………………….. all I expect for my work.",
            "description": "Kudos is singular and should be used with a singular verb.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "afd68470662a40fa9b984a9ec5cebe03"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although his speeches were …………………………., they were informative.",
            "description": "Laconic means concise or brief. It is the opposite of wordy or verbose.",
            "answers": [
                "laconic",
                "wordy",
                "verbose"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a9087c186e8e435fb8a28ddde8525372"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… I have taken to making my own clothes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Of late",
                "Lately",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8054b1a821954ceda1de2c5c1cd6e4fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "This shampoo makes a lot of ……………………………….",
            "description": "Lather means foam.",
            "answers": [
                "leather",
                "lather"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "927d983489aa4a58aa7460a868613472"
        },
        {
            "question": "I like both Mumbai and Bangalore, but I prefer the ……………………………..",
            "description": "The latter means the second of two.",
            "answers": [
                "later",
                "latter",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "266c6134411a457f84abf7a8504c7f1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Father likes to take the …………………………….. traveled roads.",
            "description": "Less can mean barely.",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "lesser",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "349057d7d0344dc8aa4ccf59f5dd3d02"
        },
        {
            "question": "Of the two actors, he is the ……………………………… known.",
            "description": "Lesser means to a smaller degree.",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "lesser",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "754a3b30df754b9c8cd56cf756dad9bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. here until the dizziness goes away.",
            "description": "Lie means rest or be flat.",
            "answers": [
                "Lie",
                "Lay",
                "Lain"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3e22d5ee43094b40b24fb3ee9888bff1"
        }
    ]
}